<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Io Levoi</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Io Levoi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Io Levoi - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:17:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nick Cave on Love</title>
      <link>/blog/nick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/nick/</guid>
      <description>“All beauty must die” Arthur Cave, the fifteen-year-old son of musician Nick Cave, accidentally fell from the 18-metre cliffs on Ovingdean Gap in Brighton, East Sussex in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Unpregnant Generation</title>
      <link>/blog/unpregnant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/unpregnant/</guid>
      <description>What Hamlet can teach us about our response to Climate Change? Our reaction to the climate crisis is very Hamletesque. We know there needs to be action, and yet we do nothing of significance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Haunted. That&#39;s why I can&#39;t write.</title>
      <link>/blog/haunted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/haunted/</guid>
      <description>My grandfather is why I can’t write. He’s also why I do write.
My grandfather has been the single most significant influence on my life. But, unfortunately, we had a falling out in late 2001, and we never spoke again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tall Poppy Syndrome</title>
      <link>/blog/tall-poppy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/tall-poppy/</guid>
      <description>What is the tall poppy syndrome? I&amp;rsquo;m yet to meet a fellow Aussie who would trade our sun-burnt land for the stars&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;stripes.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, we love yank culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Zen of Sisu</title>
      <link>/blog/zensisu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/zensisu/</guid>
      <description>There are words from other languages that cannot be easily translated into our own beautiful bastardised English. One such word, that comes from the Finns, I think encapsulates everything that we, as emerging writers, need to have.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
